Jean Ritchie and George Pickow collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound Recordings
  - Subseries 8: United States
    - AFC 2008/005: SR219, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-4. Kentucky: Church services 1. Spine: Kentucky - church. Back of the tape box: Church Service; copy; Rev. Sam Combes - Sermon; Invitation to accept God and a song - Farewell vain world; (two souls are received into God's hands?); song continued; second song; singing congregation while a preacher shouts; dismissal of the congregation to go to the [??]; [good?] people. On the reel: end of opening preacher and song /Rev. Combs sermon I /church /copy.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR220, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 5 in.
      Original ID # US-5. Kentucky: Church services 2. Spine: Kentucky church service. Back of the tape box: Combs Bend [more information crossed out]. On the reel: church service. Processor's note: the tape was received as a 5-inch reel and is now housed on a 7-inch reel.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR221, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 5 in.
      Original ID # US-6. Kentucky: Church services 3. Spine: KY - church services; US-6. Processor's note: the tape was received as a 5-inch reel and is now housed on a 7-inch reel.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR222, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-7. Kentucky: Church footwashing in Combs. Spine: KY - Foot Washing Combs KY. On the reel: FTWC.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR223, Summer 1950, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-8. Kentucky: Church footwashing in Combs. Spine: KY- Foot Wash Combs Bend KY. Back of the tape box: Old Regular Baptist Footwashing; Combs Bend Church; first Preacher - Neace; second Preacher - Wm. F. Hubbard; third Preacher - B.H. Baker.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR224, July 3, 1955, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-9. Kentucky: Church service in Jeff 1. Spine: KY Church Service in Jeff. Back of the tape box: #1, Church at Jeff, July 3, 1955; 1. Give Me Jesus; 2. I'm alone in this World; 3. O Ye Young, Ye Gay, Ye Proud; 4. Opening Remarks - Sam Combs; 5. Angels Get my Mansion Ready; 6. Prayer - Sam Combs; 7. Sermon - T.G. Bates.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR225, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-10. Kentucky: Church service in Jeff 2. Spine: KY Church Service in Jeff, KY. Back of the tape box: Church Service; Rev. Sam Combs Jeff, KY; Mrs. Sam Combs; Clifton Combs - Viper Give Me Jesus; Norman Combs - Jeff, Jesus Grant us All A Blessing; [pencil obstructed by tape]; Mr. and Mrs. [Baker?] [...]; Mallie Ritchie; Give Me Jesus; Jesus Grant us All a Blessing.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR226, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips, mono; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-11. Kentucky: Church service in Lick Branch. Spine: Kentucky Hymns - Lick Branch. Back of the tape box: Reel I; sound tapes; Cancer spots; Scene 2 - cuts 1-5; Scene 3 - cuts 1-6; Scene 4 - Cuts 1-9; George Pickow, trans. To 16 niw. On the reel: hymn sing lick branch ends 262-336 (incomplete) /MT.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR227, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-12. Kentucky: Church service in Viper. Spine: KY- Church at Viper. Back of the tape box: Hymns - Viper; 1. Give Me Jesus; 2. Jesus Grant Us All A Blessing; 3. Poor Wayfaring Stranger; Give Me Jesus for Church group. Scene. On the reel: Give Me Jesus begins blue ends white.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR228, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-13. Kentucky: Church sacred harp singing. Spine: KY Sacred Harp Singers.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR229, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-14. Kentucky: Square dance at Vicco. Spine: KY Square Dance - Video. Back of the tape box: Square Dance, Vicco, KY; Banjo, Jr. Hall; Fiddle: Bobby Summer; Guitar: Willie Hall.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR230, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-15. Kentucky: Square dance at Vicco. Spine: KY Vicco - #2.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR231, Summer 1962, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-16. Kentucky: Talk with Elijah "Boney" Combs. Spine: KY Viper "Boney" Boone's Wedding, Combs talks. Back of the tape box: Boney Combs; talk about Boone's wedding, etc.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR232, October 14, 1955, November 13, 1955, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-17. Massachusetts: Scots Guard. Spine: US - Mass. Scots Guard; Back of the tape box: copied from tape Lewis Gordon's 11/13/55; Scots Guards Band; Cambridge, Mass. October 14th, 1955; Piping; Piping - Drumming; Singing - Angus Fleming; Nov. first. Singing (Gaelic); Hugh Thorston.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR233, October 14, 1955, November 13, 1955, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-18. Massachusetts: Scots Guard. Spine: US-Mass-Scots Guard. Back of the tape box: copied from Lewis Gordon's tape 11/13/55; Scots Guards; recorded Cambridge Mass, October 14, 1955; Piping - Angus Fleming; Angus MacDonald; other pipers announce their names.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR234, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-19. New England: Chester Pipe and Drums. Spine: US - N.E. Chester Pipe and Drum. Back of the tape box: Chester Pand Corps.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR235, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20. North Carolina #1: L. Monroe Presnell (ballads). Spine: US. NC. 1; Original: July 1956. Back of the tape box: Monroe Presnell.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR236, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20a. North Carolina #2: L. Monroe Presnell (ballads). Spine: US. NC. 2; Original. Back of the tape box: M. Presnell.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR237, July 1962, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20b. North Carolina #1 and 12: Presnell and Chase. Spine: Phase Presnell: US. NC. 1 and 12; New Copy; July 1962.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR238, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20c. North Carolina #1, 2, 3, 4: L. Monroe Presnell. Spine: US. NC. 1, 2, 3, 4 Presnell; copy. On the reel: US /NC 2-3-4 N-copy.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR239, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20d. North Carolina #3: L. Monroe Presnell (ballads). Spine: US. NC. 3; Original; July 1956.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR240, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20e. North Carolina #4: L. Monroe Presnell (ballads). Spine: US. NC.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR241, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20f. North Carolina #5: Cratis Williams (hymns). Spine: US. NC. 5; Original; July 1956. Back of the tape box: Mr. Cratis Williams; ne V.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR242, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20g. North Carolina #5: Cratis Williams (hymns). Spine: US. NC. 5, Cratis Williams; copy; July 1956. Back of the tape box: Cratis Williams. On the reel: US /NC 5 copy.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR243, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20h. North Carolina #6: Cratis Williams (hymns). Spine: US. NC. 6; Original; July 1956. Back of the tape box: Mr. Williams; NC VI.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR244, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20i. North Carolina #6: Cratis Williams (hymns). Spine: US. NC. 6; copy; July 1956.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR245, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20j. North Carolina #7: Epta Baker and family (sing). Spine: US. NC. 7; Original; July 1956.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR246, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20k. North Carolina #7a: Epta Baker and family (sing). Spine: US. NC. 7; Copy A; July 1956.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR247, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20l. North Carolina #7b: Epta Baker and family (sing). Spine: US. NC. 7; Copy B; July 1956.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR248, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20m. North Carolina #7c1: Epta Baker and family (sing). Spine: US. NC. 7; Copy (C.1); July 1956.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR249, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20n. North Carolina #7c2: Epta Baker and family (sing). Spine: US. NC. 7; Copy (C.2); July 1956. Back of the tape box: Phillips; Baker; NE VIII; edited.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR250, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20o. North Carolina #7d1: Epta Baker and family (sing). Spine: US. NC. 7; Copy (D. 1); July 1956.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR251, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20p. North Carolina #7d2: Epta Baker and family (sing). Spine: US. NC. 7; Copy (D.2); July 1956. Back of the tape box: Baker; Phillips; Reid; ne; roughly edited.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR252, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20q. North Carolina #7e1: Epta Baker and family (sing). Spine: US. NC. 7; Copy (E.1); July 1956.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR253, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20r. North Carolina #7e2: Epta Baker and family (sing). Spine: US. NC. 7; Copy (E2); July 1956. Back of the tape box: Lookabill; Phillips; Baker; Reid; neIX; edited, Caldwell Co.; Mark Tape.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR254, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20s. North Carolina #8: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 8; Original: 7 1/2; July 1956. Back of the tape box: R. Chase; ne XII; Mountain Folk Tales; R. Chase description of tale-telling in Southern Cobin; 1. Like meat loves salt (well the old Rug went to his next oldest daughter - Repeated). (The two oldest girls husbands - Repeat). (So she brought that salt - Repeat) Repeat of ending; 2. Tall Tales; 3. The Tall [cornstalks?] (well the sun ball had-Repeat); 4. different ending; 5. different beginning; 6. ending of Skoonkin huntin; 7. Repeat of beginning of Skoonkin Huntin; 8. beginning of Skoonkin hunting.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR255, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20t. North Carolina #8: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 8; Copy a; July 1956. Back of the tape box: R. Chase.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR256, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20u. North Carolina #9: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 9 Chase; Original: 7 1/2; July 1956. Back of the tape box: Chase.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR257, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20v. North Carolina #9: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 9: July 1956. Back of the tape box: Richard Chase. On the reel: US/NC 9 copy.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR258, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20w. North Carolina #10: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 10; Original: July 1956. Back of the tape box: Richard Chase; ne XI; Mountain Folk Tales.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR259, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20x. North Carolina #10a: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 10; Copy [A]. Back of the tape box: R. Chase.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR260, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20y. North Carolina #10b: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 10; Copy [B]; July 1956. Back of the tape box: R. Chase.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR261, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20z. North Carolina #10c: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 10; Copy [c]: 15; July 1956. Back of the tape box: Wicked John; Sound Track (Sync) for Story Telling Sequence; Chase on Film. Also [Whimmiddle?].
    - AFC 2008/005: SR262, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20aa. North Carolina #10d: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 10; Copy [D]; T3 copy. Back of the tape box: R. Chase.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR263, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20bb. North Carolina #11: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 11; original; July 1956. Back of the tape box: Signet Book Record; R. Chase.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR264, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20cc. North Carolina #11: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 11; copy; July 1956. Back of the tape box: Chase.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR265, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20dd. North Carolina #12: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 12; original; 1956. Back of the tape box: R. Chase - Songs [more information crossed out].
    - AFC 2008/005: SR266, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 in.
      Original ID # US-20ee. North Carolina #13: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 13; original. Back of the tape box: R. Chase; Liam Clancy. Processor's note: the tape was received as a 5-inch reel and is now housed on a 7-inch reel.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR267, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20ff. North Carolina #14: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: US. NC. 14; original. Back of the tape box: R. Chase; Mountain Tales for Signet Book; [crossed out]; Jack and old Lush X; hike landscape X; [3 titles crossed out]; Riddle #1 (Man with one eye); Riddle #2 (thorn); Answer #2 Pal and the City-Bullies.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR268, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-20gg. North Carolina #14: Richard Chase (mountain tales). Spine: NC-14; Copy.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR377, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-21. Oklahoma: Gospel Singing. On the reel: unknown gospel.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR378, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 5 in.
      Original ID # US-21a. Pennsylvania: Anonymous storyteller in Pittsburgh. Spine: Folk Stories Pittsburgh. Front of the tape box: [information crossed out]. On the reel: Pittsburgh. Processor's note: the tape was received as a 5-inch reel and is now housed on a 7-inch reel.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR379, possibly 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-22. South Carolina: gospel singing. US. SC. 1; Original 19[56?]. Back of the tape box: S. Carolina Copy; Church.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR380, possibly 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-23. South Carolina: gospel singing. Spine: US. SC. 1; Copy C: 7 1/2; 19[56?]; S. Carolina no. 18 copy; SC church.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR381, 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-23a. South Carolina: gospel singing. Spine: US. SC. 1; Copy A; 1956.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR382, 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-23b. South Carolina: gospel singing. Spine: US. SC. 1; T 2 copy; gospel group. On the reel: US/SC 1 copy B.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR383, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-24. Virginia #1: Hobart Smith sings. Spine: US. Va. 1; original; July 1956. Back of the tape box: VA III; Hobart Smith; edited.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR384, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-24a. Virginia #1: Hobart Smith sings. Spine: U.S. VA 1; copy; July 1956; Va. No. 15 copy.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR385, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-25. Virginia #2: Horton Barker. Spine: US. Va. 2; Original: 15; 1956: July. Back of the tape box: Va. I; Horton Barker; edited; US/VA 2 part. orig.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR386, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-25a. Virginia #2: Horton Barker. Spine: Us. Va. 2; Copy; 1956 July; Va. 16 copy. Back of the tape box: H. Baker.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR387, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-26. Virginia #3: Texas Gladden. Spine: US. Va. 3; Original: 15; July 1956; Va. no. 17. Back of the tape box: Va. V; Mrs. Texas A. Gladden; edited. On the reel: US/VA 3 /part. orig.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR388, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-26a. Virginia #3: Texas Gladden. Spine: US. Va. 3; copy; July 1956; Va. no. 17 copy.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR389, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-26b. Virginia: copy of #2 and 3. Spine: VA 2 and 3; copy; July 1956; Va. 2 and 3 N-copy.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR390, July 1956, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # US-27. Virginia: #4. Spine: UA. Va. 4; Original: 15; July 1956. Back of the tape box: VA IV; Hobart Smith; banjo, voice, Fiddle; Fragments cut from Instrumental album at beginning. Save!!
  - Subseries 9: Various international recordings
    - AFC 2008/005: SR269, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # INT-1. France, Biarritz Festival - Basque performers. Spine: INT-1. Tape box Front of the tape box: Basque in Frontor #1; Oedarra.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR270, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # INT-2. France, Biarritz Festival - Basque performers. Spine: Biarritz Fest. #2; INT-2. Front of the tape box: Basque in Frouton #2; performers at Biarritz Festival; Oldarra; mostly choral.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR271, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # INT-3. France, Biarritz Festival - Basque performers. Spine: Biarritz Folk Fest. Basque Performers. Back of the tape box: of the tape box: Beri-Frouton rec - Score - calling and following at [...] at paper #1; Pelota Helene - LasLoule; Dancing groups Basque; after Pelota - the "Bear - Napoleanic" dance; music - not interesting; Paper #2 - Flute tune introduces Basque dancers; Flute and drums tunes - good, and good tunes; applause after ea. Solo dance (probably high-kickers); March off- music soft and louder. Break in middle; Intro by Man - then wife - [...] dance. On the reel: Basque Festival at Frouton.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR272, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # INT-4. France, Biarritz Festival - Basque performers. Spine: Biarritz Folk Fest. Back of the tape box: of the tape box: Japan - Good; Yugoslavia. On the reel: empty 1.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR273, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # INT-5. Mexico, recordings of Indians. Spine: Mexico Indians. Back of the tape box: of the tape box: [???]; 1. Jean - 12 Days; 2. Itty Bitty Baby; 3. Cherry Tree; 4. 12 Days; 1. Gypsy Davy - a capella; 2. [...] and 3. [...] - horrible guitar; 4. Mexican explanation "Le Chuiparosa"; 5. "Wakelly"; 6. Drum and fife and maypole.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR274, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # INT-6. Mexico, recordings of Indians. Mexico - Double Track.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR275, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 5 in.
      Original ID # INT-7. Mexico, recordings of Indians. Spine: Mexico. Back of the tape box: of the tape box: Jean's B.B.C. Record; Mexico - ?. Processor's note: the tape was received as a 5-inch reel and is now housed on a 7-inch reel.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR276, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 15 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # INT-8. Spine: Russian Songs.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR277, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # INT-9. Spain, Pamplona Festival #1: Indonesia, Switzerland, England. Spine: Pamplona Festival -1, Spain; Reel #1 Pamplona Festival - [...]. On the reel: Span [sic] /Casino Yugoslav Indonese.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR278, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # INT-10. Spain, Pamplona Festival #2: England, America (Jean Ritchie), Finland, Spain; France. 1 - English; Jean; Finland; Spanish Guitar - castanets; French pipes. Front of the tape box: Reel #2 Pamplona Festival - Jean; English; Jean; Finland; Spanish guitar and castanets; French pipes.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR279, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # INT-11. Spain, Pamplona Festival #3: Spain, Holland, Japan. Spine: Pamplona Festival - 3, Spain. Front of the tape box: Pamplona #3 - Festival - might - P3FN; Spanish Valincic; Holland; Japan.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR280, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # INT-12. Spain, Pamplona Festival #4: Turkey, Spain. Spine: Pamplona Festival. Front of the tape box: Pamplona Festival #4; Turkey; Spain - de Jaem.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR281, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # INT-13. Spain, Pamplona Festival: copy of INT9. Spine: Spain - Pamplona Festival. Front of the tape box: Pamplona No. I; Indonesian; Alpenhorns; Girls Slow Yodel; English. On the reel: #1 it Pamplona Indonese-Swiss English.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR282, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # INT-14. Spain, Pamplona Festival: compilation Swiss yodel and Irish. Spine: Swiss (?) Yodel and Irish. On the reel: Swiss? Yodel /7 1⁄2 /Irish and Gaelic 15.
  - Subseries 10: Recordings: lectures and workshops
    - AFC 2008/005: SR283, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # LE-1. Dulcimers workshop.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR284, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # LE-2. Dulcimer instruction - J.R. On the reel: Dulcimer instruction - Jean Ritchie.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR285, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # LE-3. Jean Ritchie - Dulcimer Side 1 and 2.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR286, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # LE-4. Jean Ritchie Lecture in Ireland.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR287, May 15, 1959, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, single track; 7 in.
      Original ID # LE-5. Jean Ritchie Lecture at old Chelsea School - Tape 1. Copy tape; Jean Ritchie Lecture at old Chelsea School- May 15, 1959, Tape 1.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR288, May 15, 1959, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, single track; 7 in.
      Original ID # LE-6. Jean Ritchie Lecture at old Chelsea School - Tape 2. Copy tape; Jean Ritchie Lecture at old Chelsea School - May 15, 1959, Tape 2.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR289, May 15, 1959, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, single track; 7 in.
      Original ID # LE-7. Jean Ritchie Lecture at old Chelsea School - Tape 4. Copy tape; Jean Ritchie Lecture at old Chelsea School - May 15, 1959, Tape 4.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR290, May 15, 1959, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, single track; 7 in.
      Original ID # LE-8. Jean Ritchie Lecture at old Chelsea School - Tape 3. Copy tape; Jean Ritchie Lecture at the hold Chelsea School - May 15, 1959, Tape 3.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR291, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.
      Original ID # LE-9. Song Collecting Workshop. 1. Banks Red Roses; 2. Cuckoo's Nest; 3. Bog in Valley; 4. Barbara Allen (both versions two verses of ea); 5. Uncle Frog; 6. Orange and Lemon; 7. Maid [in] Garden; 8. When my Apron Hung Low; Dec. 2.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR487, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      NOTE NUMBER SEQUENCE Original ID # LE-10. On container: Jean's talk about Church; Wayfarin [sic] Stranger - Old Regulars; voice-over tests - Jean. On the reel: Wayfarin [sic] Stranger /Church /Jean part narra SF /S.F. church.
  - Subseries 11: Anthology
    - AFC 2008/005: SR292, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # AN-1. Anthology Collected Ballad Compilation.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR293, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # AN-2. Anthology Ballads Comp. On the reel: Anthology / Ballads No. 2 up to mark /Ballads No. 3 - 3 songs /Lazy Farmer Boy - 4th song in.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR294, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Original ID # AN-3. Copy of some anthology records. Processor's note: the tape was received as a 5-inch reel and is now housed on a 7-inch reel.
    - AFC 2008/005: SR295, 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, single track; 7 in.